# Gauray Tamhan

gtamhan3@gatech.edu | (770) 570-6895 | linkedin.com/in/gauravtamhan

#### Profile

Front-end developer with 3+ years of experience building and maintaining both web and mobile apps. Passionate about UX and design, backed by experience in industry and team projects. Seeking a full-time role starting in Summer 2020.

#### Skills

Development: HTML/CSS, JavaScript, React, Redux, Vue, SASS, D3, Node, Webpack, iQuery, MySQL

Practices: Agile Development, SCRUM, Git, RESTful APIs, JWT, Responsive Web Design

**Design Tools:** Photoshop, Sketch, Adobe XD, InVision

# Experience

Graduate Research Assistant in CSPAV at Georgia Tech

August 2019 - December 2019

- Worked with lead designer to translate design mockups into a viable product given budget, resource, and time constraints.
- Lead development of a data visualization app using React, Mapbox, D3, and JWT for authentication.

Front End Developer at Fitspot Wellness, Atlanta

May 2018 - July 2019

- Designed and implemented 4 new features for the primary customer web portal.
- Built and deployed a mobile-first designed, progressive web app using React Redux architecture.
- Built reusable and scalable modules, performed bug fixes, and conducted code reviews.

Software Engineering Intern at JDA Software Inc, Roswell

January 2016 - August 2017

- Developed, maintained, and tested a full-stack web application that handles workforce management of large scale retailers using C#, SQL, and Visual Studio.
- Upgraded infrastructure for products, documented procedures, and performed bug fixes.

### **Projects**

## React Native Cross Platform App

April 2019

• Built a small scale marketplace that allows users to post, manage, and complete tasks using React Native, Node, Firebase, Expo, and PayPal API.

Website Redesign for Georgia Tech iOS Club

March 2018

• Designed and developed a responsive, mobile friendly site using Bootstrap and Jekyll.

#### Data Visualization Tool

May 2017

 Built a data visualization tool using D3 and College Scorecard data to assist high school students research college admission statistics.

#### Education

Georgia Institute of Technology

- M.S. Human Computer Interaction
- August 2018 May 2020 • B.S. Computer Science

December 2017